[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":127726,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":269746,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":30909,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":300663,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":17696,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":318386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1742,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":320131,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":6989,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":327122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2050,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":329176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the sec ond one  to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":12288,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":341467,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1362,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":342833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4864,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":347699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1336,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":349038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":352969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<s ub>6</su b> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1060,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":354032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4584,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":358617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1050,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":359668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <b r /><br  /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3979,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":363648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1027,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":364676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your  result.) ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":368229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1225,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":369457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4206,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":373664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1249,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":374915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":7711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":382628,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1213,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":383843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":30989,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":414836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own  inverse  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":117138,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":531976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I don't know. I didn' tunder","6"],"rt":32932,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":564914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":11704,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":576622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What  is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":9747,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":586371,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1589,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":587962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":8666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":596630,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1786,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":598419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":7974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":606394,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 bec ause 2 + <sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1380,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":607775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":5247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":613023,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3121,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":616146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to succes sively a pply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":8924,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":625073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 + <sub>6</ sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":71835,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":696913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":4729,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":701648,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1677,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":703327,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5  a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":21336,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":724665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1360,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":726027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10 -0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4988,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":731018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1127,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":732147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":735651,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1123,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":736775,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8 .<br />< br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":25984,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":762761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":4821,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":767587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1138,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":768728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3099,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":771830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":776877,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":11691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":788570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3296,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":791870,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4952,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":796823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":15466,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":812292,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"Four plus one is five and that's smaller than 9, so that's the answer.","explanation_history":["5 ","5","4 + 1 is ","Four plus one is five and that's smaller than 9, so that's the anwwe","Four plus one is five and that's smaller than 9, so that's the anww","Four plus one is five and that's smaller than 9, so that's the anw","Four plus one is five and that's smaller than 9, so that's the answer."],"response_history":["4","3","5"],"rt":22849,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":835142,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than nine. Twelve minus nine is three.","explanation_history":["Eight plus 5","Eight plus four is twelve ","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than 9. ","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than 9.","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than 9","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than nine. Tweleve","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than nine. Twelev","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than nine. Twele","Eight plus four is twelve, which is bigger than nine. Twelve minus nine is three."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":39450,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":874594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm pretty sure it's  because  zero is always the identity.","explanation_history":["I don';t ","I don';t","I don';","I don't know.","I'm pretty sure it's because 0","I'm pretty sure it's because zero is always the inde","I'm pretty sure it's because zero is always the ind","I'm pretty sure it's because zero is always the in","I'm pretty sure it's because zero is always the identity."],"response_history":["I don't know.","0"],"rt":29462,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":904059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Fo","F","4"],"rt":27598,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":931661,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":4976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":936642,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":2981,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":939625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"Nine minus three is six.","explanation_history":["9","Nine minus three is six."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":16141,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":955770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Adding two to itself multiple times doesn't give you all of the numbers.","explanation_history":["I can't rmee","I can't rme","I can't rm","I can't remember what a generator ","I can't remember what a generator","I can't remember what a generator is, so I just guessed.","I don't know how to erxp","I don't know how to erx","I don't know how to er","I don't know how to explain it.","I added to to","I added to t","I added to ","I added to","I added two to is","I added two to itself and it ","I added two to itself a","I added two to itself ","I added two to itselfa","I added two to itself a few times and it came  u","I added two to itself a few times and it came  ","I added two to itself  a few t imes and it came up under nine.","Adding two to in","Adding two to is","Adding two to itlsef","Adding two to itlse","Adding two to itls","Adding two to itl","Adding two to itself multiple times doesn't give you all of the numbers?","Adding two to itself multiple times doesn't give you all of the numbers. ","Adding two to itself multiple times doesn't give you all of the numbers."],"response_history":["No","Yes","No"],"rt":151742,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1107514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Adding three multiple times to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","explanation_history":["I","Adding three to itself d","Adding three to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three  to  itself d oesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three m to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three mu to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three mul to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multi to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multipl to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multiple to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multiple  to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multiple ti to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multiple tim to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers.","Adding three multiple times to itself doesn't give you all of the numbers."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":27785,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1135302,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your a nswer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm pretty sure the only generator is 1.","explanation_history":["I'm pretty sure the on","I'm pretty sure the only generator is 1."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":23902,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1159207,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"Adding 6 to itself is higher than 9.","explanation_history":["Se","S","Same as previous asn","Same as previous as","Same as previous answers: Adding 6 to itself is higher","Same as previous answers: Adding 6 to itself is h","Adding 6 to iu","Adding 6 to itself is higher than 9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":33821,"trial_type":"quest ion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1193032,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":25183,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1218220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Beats the fuck out of.","Beats the fuck out of me.","I have no idea.","9"],"rt":33350,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1251575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"1 +_n x","explain":true,"explanation":"I really don't understand this, so I just guessed.","explanation_history":["I really don't understand this ","I really don't understand this, so I just guees","I really don't understand this, so I just guee","I really don't understand this, so I just guessed."],"response_history":["1","1 + _","1 + ","1 +_N","1 +_n x"],"rt":43472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1295052,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I hav e absolutely no idea.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I rfe","I rf","I really don't n","I really don't know.","I have abo","I have absolutely no idea."],"rt":51677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1346731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":4493,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1351227,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":3703,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1354934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":12222,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1367160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"False","explain":true,"explanation":"I just guessed. I'm so confused about all  the ter minology.","explanation_history":["I just guessed. I don't","I just guessed. I'm so f","I just guessed. I'm so confused.","I just guessed. I'm so confused, ","I just guessed. I'm so confused,","I just guessed. I'm so confused about all the terminology."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":42443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1409608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1414498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a  generato r under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"Again, I had to just guess since I have no idea.","explanation_history":["Again, just guessed.","Again, I had to just guess since I have no idea."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":32019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1446520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":3569,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1450092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1401,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1451495,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"41","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["41"],"rt":2362,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1453859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2739,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1456601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Algebra (which I failed and had to take in summer school, and still barely passed).","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Algebra (which I failed and had to take in summer school, and still barely b","Algebra (which I failed and had to take in summer school, and still barely passed)>","Algebra (which I failed and had to take in summer school, and still barely passed)."],"rt":25942,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1482544,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2352,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1484899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2396,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1487297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2585,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1489886,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat"],"rt":3027,"trial_type":"question ","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1492915,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2502,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1495419,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1497488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"f ree","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":4530,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1502021,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No."],"rt":3533,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1505560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I hope because I'm a math dummy that I don't get rejected. I did try.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I hope because I'm a mah","I hope because I'm a math dummy that  I don't  get rejected. I did try,.","I hope because I'm a math dummy that I don't get rejected. I did try,","I hope because I'm a math dummy that I don't get rejected. I did try."],"rt":19162,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1524724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]